http://shelterlogic.com/privacy-policy/

What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our website, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. This is done to process orders, verify your identity, and/or provide you with an optimal user and consumer experience.When ordering or registering on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our website anonymously. Some of the information we collect may include any of the following:Identifiers, such as your name, IP address, email, and other similar identifiers;Personal information such as payment information;Characteristics about you, such as age and gender;Inferenced based information we collect to better understand your preferences and behavior, including to customize content and advertising for you.We sometimes work with third party vendors and applications such as Google, Bing, AdRoll and other advertisers that use cookies to serve ads online. Many of these third party vendors use of the DART cookie enables them to serve ads to websites across the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. For residents of California wishing to opt out of cookies and wanting to learn more about cookie compliance, see below.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To personalize your experience – Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.To improve our website – We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.To improve customer service – Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To process transactions – Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site featureTo send periodic emails – The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act also known as “CCPA”.  If you have registered as a user on ShelterLogic.com, opted into marketing emails, filled out forms or requests, or placed an order, please note that general information about you may have been collected in an effort to provide you with an optimum user and consumer experience. It is possible that we may disclose certain information we collect about you for purposes that may be considered a “sale” under the CCPA. For example, we may disclose information to advertising partners, advertising technology companies, and companies that perform advertising-related services in order to provide you with more relevant advertising tailored to your product interests. Learn more about CCPA and specifically how we may use your information below.As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at any time by logging into their control panel and going to the “Edit Profile” page.Under the CCPA, California residents have the right to opt out of the “sale” of their personal information. We provide this right, subject to a verifiable consumer request, to account holders regarding personal information collected by us in connection with your account, including any profiles.You may access your customer account by visiting your profile and logging into your ShelterLogic.com account, here.If you are a California resident, you may request and obtain a removal of all content or information you have submitted on Shelterlogic.com.For more information about removing your data, or accessing a file of all the information we have on you, click here.For more information about CCPA and data removal, click below:CCPA InformationDo Not Sell My Information and California Privacy Rights ShelterLogic Group and ShelterLogic Group brands respect your privacy. We are committed to providing you with meaningful choices with respect to the information we collect from/and/or about you. Beginning January 1, 2020, the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (the “CCPA”) provides California residents with certain rights with respect to their personal information, including the right to opt out of certain disclosures of personal information as explained below.In interacting on our website or purchasing any of our products from us directly, ShelterLogic Group may collect information from or about you, including personal information, when you interact on our website, make a purchase from any and all of our website(s), request information from our customer support department, opt into marketing emails, or request information about any one of our products. You can read more about how and when we request information from you as described in our Privacy Policy. If you have registered as a user on ShelterLogic.com, we may disclose certain information we collect about you for purposes that may be considered a “sale” under the CCPA. For example, we may disclose information to advertising partners, advertising technology companies, and companies that perform advertising-related services in order to provide you with more relevant advertising tailored to your product interests.Under the CCPA, you have the right to opt out of the “sale” of your personal information. We provide this right, subject to a verifiable consumer request, to account holders regarding personal information collected by us in connection with your account, including any profiles. To exercise this right, please fill out this Data Subject Request form.A designated support representative will review your opt-out request and will respond to you within 45 days.If you are not a registered user or customer of ShelterLogic.com or our websites, we may have limited information about you and do not “sell” your information as described above. However, you have choices regarding how third parties may collect and use data about you from the methods described below.Please note that this opt-out will apply on a going forward basis with respect to our disclosure of information. Even if you opt out, you may continue to receive ads on ShelterLogic.com which may or may not be as tailored to your interests.In addition to providing you the ability to opt out of the “sale” of your personal information under CCPA as described above, you have additional controls and choices with respect to the collection and use of your information by third parties:Some of the third parties that collect information from or about you on ShelterLogic.com in order to provide more relevant advertising to you participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising and/or may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). To make choices about the use of information from or about you for online behavioral or interest-based advertising on websites (desktop and mobile browsers), please visit the DAA and the NAI.For more information about these and additional controls and choices available to you, please see Section 6 of our Privacy Policy.If you have any questions regarding ShelterLogic.com’s data sharing practices, please contact us using the Contact Us page.If you are a California resident, the following additional rights may be available to you.If you are a California resident under the age of 18 and a customer or registered user of the ShelterLogic.com, you may request information and obtain removal of content or information you have submitted to ShelterLogic Group. If you would like to exercise this right, please fill out the form here.Beginning January 1, 2020, the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) provides California residents with additional rights as described below. Please note your right to know and right to delete are subject to certain exceptions under the CCPA.Disclosures About Your Personal InformationWe utilize services that may collect the following categories of personal information, as defined in the CCPA, from or about you and may have disclosed this information for a business purpose:Identifiers, such as your name, IP address, email, and other similar identifiers;Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records provision, such as payment information;Characteristics about you, such as age and gender;Inferenced based on the information we collect from or about you which we use to better understand your preferences and behavior, including to customize Content and advertising for you.Our Privacy Policy includes additional information about our data practices. You can learn more about the categories of personal information we collect from or about you and the categories of sources from which we collect this information, the business or commercial purposes for collecting this information in, and the categories of third parties with whom we have shared personal information for a business purpose.Right to Know: You have the right to request that we disclose to you the categories and specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you as well as information about how we collect, use, disclose, and “sell” personal information.Right to Delete: You have the right to request the deletion of personal information that we collect or maintain about you and your account. Please note that requesting deletion will require the cancellation and deletion of your account which, upon completion, cannot be undone.Right to Opt Out of “Sale” ShelterLogic Group and ShelterLogic Group Brands may disclose certain information about you if you are a registered user of the ShelterLogic.com or if you have registered a purchase on our website(s) or contacted customer support, or opted into marketing emails and communications with ShelterLogic Group and any ShelterLogic Group brands for purposes that may be considered a “sale” under the CCPA. For example, we may disclose information to advertising partners, advertising technology companies, and companies that perform advertising-related services in order to provide you with more relevant advertising tailored to your interests on ShelterLogic Group brands and products. This information may include identifiers such as your IP address, advertising identifiers, your email address (in a de-identified or hashed form), age and gender, your internet or other electronic network information such as your interaction with an ad, and geolocation data.SafariClick Safari in the menu bar.Click Preferences.Click the Privacy panel.For the option Cookies and website data, select Always allow.Internet ExplorerClick the cog/tools menu icon in the upper right of the window.Click Internet Options.Click the Privacy tab.Click SitesIn the Address of website field enter [*].shelterlogic.com. Be sure to include the square brackets before and after the asterisk.Click Allow, then OK.ChromeClick the menu icon in the upper right side of the browser window.Click Settings.Click Show advanced settings.Click Content settings.Ensure the option Allow local data to be set (recommended) is selected.Click Manage exceptions.In the field labeled Hostname pattern enter [*.]shelterlogic.com. Be sure to include the square brackets before and after the asterisk.Leave the Behavior drop down set to Allow, then click Done.FirefoxClick the menu icon.Open the Options window.For Windows users, click Options.For Mac OS users, click Preferences.Click the Privacy panel.In the History section, select Firefox will: Remember history.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.This policy was last modified on 1/3/2020.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.ShelterLogic Group
150 Callender Road
Watertown, Connecticut 06795
Download the SP Series Building Case Study + Product BrochureTo download the full case study and product brochure, please provide a little information about yourself below.
X Grow Higher with ShelterTech High Tunnel GreenhousesDownload the ShelterTech High Tunnel Greenhouse product guide and learn how it can help you grow strong plants faster and more efficiently.
X Sign Up for Factory Sale RemindersWe know you’re busy.  Sign up to receive email reminders for the ShelterLogic Fall Factory Sale on October 13th, 2018 from 8:00 AM – 3:00 PM.
X Hello!Please allow us a 10 BUSINESS DAY lead time on requests.If your request is under the 10 BUSINESS DAY MINIMUM we will determine priority of the project and will be in touch with estimated completion time.
× Sign Up for RemindersWe will email you when the Sequoia Gazebo and Redwood Gazebo become available.
Lost your password?
Forgotten Password
Cancel
